

JOSE GUZMAN

Android & Front End Developer

Phone 1 (809) 769 - 3831

Email ariel.guzman01@gmail

LinkedIn https://linkedin.com/in/

jose-ariel-guzman peralta-0ba21b171

Address

Santo Domingo, República Dominicana

Skills

JavaScript Play

Java

Framework

Kotlin

HTLM

Android

CSS

Sass

Angular

NodeJS

jQuery

Recent Professional Experience

Senior Software Developer, Newtech S.R.L - August, 2016 -Today

- Code cohesive software for Verizon internal use.
- Migrate old software made in JSF to Angular or ExtJS.
- Development of products such as ChatBots with the usage of IBM Watson

Full Stack Developer. Media Revolution - April, 2014 - August, 2016

- Manage the Android and Javascript team.
- Develop clean and reusable code using Java and Javascript
- Provide feedback on the design and creation of new products.

Education

Licenciatura en Informática 2011-2019 (Computer Science), Universidad Católica Santo Domingo SANTO DOMINGO, REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA.

About Me

Experienced Android developer with Kotlin and Java as well as hybrid mobile development with frameworks such as Ionic Framework and Cordova/PhoneGap. Seasoned web developer using frameworks such as Angular (all versions) and backends with NodeJS and Play framework.

References

Alfredo Rivera Development Manager +1 (809) 459 - 0008

Snailin Inoa Senior Software Engineer Team Lead +1 (809) 419 - 1923